<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<questions><category name="PERCEPTION"><question>Do you think I've ever been in love?</question><question>What about me is the most strange or unfamiliar?</question><question>Do you think I've ever had my heart broken?</question><question>What do you think I'd splurge on?</question><question>What do you think my major is?</question><question>What do you think I'm going to do in the future (work/employment)?</question><question>What was your first impression of me?</question><question>Do you think I was popular in high school?</question><question>On a scale of 1 - 10, how messy do you think my car is?</question><question>Do you think I like hot cheetos?</question><question>Do you think I like to read?</question><question>Do you think I'm in Greek Life?</question><question>Do you think I have a sibling? Older or younger?</question><question>Who do you think my favorite artist is?</question><question>Where do you think I grew up?</question><question>What do you think my favorite Starbucks drink is?</question><question>Do you think I like Taco Bell?</question></category><category name="CONNECTION"><question>What's the last thing you lied about?</question><question>What is your most defining characteristic?</question><question>Are you lying to yourself about anything?</question><question>How are you, really?</question><question>What is your least favorite personality trait in a person?</question><question>When is the last time you felt lucky to be you?</question><question>Which one of your parent's personality traits do you want to keep/ let go of?</question><question>What would you tell your younger self and what have you learned from this lesson?</question><question>What's the worst pain you've ever been in that wasn't physical?</question><question>What's your dad's name and one thing about him?</question><question>What's the most unexplainable thing that has ever happened to you?</question><question>What would your younger self not believe about your life today?</question><question>What non-domestic animal describes you and why?</question><question>What are you still trying to prove to yourself?</question><question>What is your favorite adjective with which to be described?</question><question>When is the last time you cried?</question><question>If you could instill one personality trait in your kid, what would it be?</question><question>What's the hardest part about dating you?</question><question>What's your favorite song lyric that you can think of off the top of your head?</question><question>Think of someone that you admire. What made you think about them specifically?</question><question>What's the biggest mistake you've made?</question><question>What's a phrase that you say that you wish you would stop saying?</question></category><category name="REFLECTION"><question>Based on what you learned about me what would you recommend I read?</question><question>What about me surprised you?</question><question>Based on what you know about me, do you have a Netflix recommendation?</question><question>What do you think our most important similarities are?</question><question>What do you think my superpower is?</question><question>What do you think is one thing I could do that would drastically improve my life?</question><question>What would be the perfect gift for me?</question><question>How would you describe me to a stranger?</question><question>What do I need to hear right now?</question><question>Based on what you've learned about me, does my social media portray me accurately?</question><question>What is a lesson you will take away from our conversation?</question><question>What can I help you with?</question><question>What do you think do I fear the most?</question><question>Where am I most qualified to give advice about?</question><question>What about me is the hardest for you to understand?</question><question>If we were a band what would be our name?</question><question>Admit something</question><question>What parts of yourself do you see in me?</question><question>How does one earn your vulnerability?</question><question>Dare your partner to do something out of their comfort zone next week.</question><question>What do you recommend I should let go of?</question><question>What has this conversation taught you about yourself?</question><question>What do you think my defining characteristic is?</question><question>Why do you think we met?</question><question>What question were you most afraid to answer?</question><question>When this game is over, what will be something you will remember about me?</question><question>What do you think my weakness is?</question><question>How do our personalities compliment each other?</question><question>What would make you feel closer to me?</question><question>What do you think I should know about myself that perhaps I'm unaware of?</question><question>What do you admire most about me?</question><question>In one word, describe how you feel right now.</question><question>Do you believe everyone has a calling? If so, do you think I've found mine?</question><question>What do you think my defining characteristic is?</question><question>What can we create together?</question><question>What answer of mine made you light up?</question><question>What's the most attractive quality about me that isn't physical?</question><question>Based on what you learned re-write each other's dating app bios. (30 sec)</question></category><category name="WILDCARD"><question>Based on what you learned re-write each other's dating app bios. (30 sec)</question><question>DRAW A PICTURE TOGETHER (30 SECS)</question><question>LOOK INTO EACH OTHER'S EYES FOR 30 SECONDS. WHAT DID YOU NOTICE?</question><question>WRITE A MESSAGE TO EACH OTHER AND GIVE IT TO EACH OTHER. OPEN IT ONCE YOU HAVE LEFT.</question><question>THINK OF YOUR FAVOURITE CHILDHOOD TV SHOW OF ALL TIME, ON THE COUNT OF THREE SAY IT OUTLOUD (BOTH PLAYERS)</question><question>TAKE A SELFIE TOGETHER</question><question>STARING CONTEST. FIRST-PERSON TO BLINK MUST REVEAL A PERSONAL PROBLEM AND ASK THE OTHER FOR ADVICE ON HOW THEY MIGHT HANDLE IT.</question><question>CREATE YOUR OWN QUESTION. ANYTHING. MAKE IT COUNT.</question><question>TELL THE OTHER PERSON TO CLOSE THEIR EYES AND TO KEEP THEM CLOSED. (WAIT 10 SECONDS. DESCRIBE TO THEM IN DETAIL YOUR FAVOURITE MEMORY OF THEM/ TWO OF YOU)</question><question>PRESS SHUFFLE ON YOUR MUSIC LIBRARY. EXPLAIN THE FIRST SONG THAT COMES UP!</question><question>LET GO OF YOUR ATTACHMENT TO THE OUTCOME wildcard character - BOTH PLAYERS SHARE SOMETHING YOU'RE MOST GRATEFUL FOR IN THIS CURRENT MOMENT.</question><question>DRAW YOUR CURRENT FEELINGS THEN COMPARE.</question><question>SHOW THE FIRST PHOTO IN YOUR CAMERA ROLL. EXPLAIN.</question><question>THINK OF SOMETHING THAT YOU DISLIKE THAT MOST PEOPLE DON'T. ON THE COUNT OF 3 SAY IT OUTLOUD.</question><question>SHARE A FAVOURITE MEMORY OF YOURS. COMPARE. (BOTH)</question><question>SING YOUR FAVOURITE SONG LYRICS YOU CAN THINK OF OFF THE TOP OF YOUR HEAD. (BOTH)</question><question>HOW CAN I ADD 1% MORE HAPPINESS IN YOUR LIFE?</question></category></questions>